pop-japan.com 2016-10-30

# POP JAPAN

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy oversees the manner in which Pop Japan collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from user of this website. This privacy policy applies to the site and all products and services offered by Pop Japan.

Personal Identification Information

This site may collect personal identification information of the users, as appropriate, such as name, email address, mailing address, and phone number in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register on the site, and connect with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. However, users may visit our site anonymously. For this, we will collect personal identification information from the users, only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to provide their personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information, such as the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users’ means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers and other similar information whenever they visit and have dealings with our site.

Web browser cookies

Our site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and occasionally, to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

How we use collected information?

Pop Japan may collect and use user’s personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service
  * The information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

How we protect your information?

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Changes to this privacy policy

Pop Japan has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will notify you through the email address you provided. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we help to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

Contact Us

We’d love to hear from you! If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, and/or your dealings with this site, reach us through the following contact details:
